const CP_MCQS = {
    mcq1: [
        {
          id: "1",
          subject_name: "CP",
          chapter_name: "Mcqs in CS",
          question: "Choose the correct statment",
          option_one: "Use of <i> goto</i> enhances the logical clarity of a code",
          option_two: "Use of <i> goto</i> makes the debugging task easier",
          option_three: "Use  <i> goto</i> when you want to jump out of a nested loop ",
          option_four: "Never use goto",
          answer: "C",
          explanation: "<a target='_blank' href='https://www.avatto.com/computer-science/test/mcqs/questions-answers/c/20/2.html'> Another mcqs link </a>"
            },
      ],
      mcq2: [
        {
          id: "2",
          subject_name: "CP",
          chapter_name: "Mcqs in CS",
          question: "Which is true of conditional compliation?",
          option_one: "It is compiling a program based on a condition",
          option_two: "It is taken care of by the pre-processor",
          option_three: "Both option A and B",
          option_four: "None of the mentioned ",
          answer: "C",
          explanation: ""
            },
      ],
      mcq3: [
        {
          id: "3",
          subject_name: "CP",
          chapter_name: "Mcqs in CS",
          question: "C was primarly developed as a",
          option_one: "systems programming language",
          option_two: "general purpose language",
          option_three: "data processing language",
          option_four: "none of the above",
          answer: "A",
          explanation: ""
            },
      ],
      mcq4: [
        {
          id: "4",
          subject_name: "CP",
          chapter_name: "Mcqs in CS",
          question: "C is a",
          option_one: "high level language",
          option_two: "low level language",
          option_three: "high level language with some low level features",
          option_four: "low level language with some high level features",
          answer: "C",
          explanation: ""
            },
      ],
      mcq5: [
        {
          id: "5",
          subject_name: "CP",
          chapter_name: "Mcqs in CS",
          question: "Even if a particular implementation does not limit the number of characters in an identifier, it is advisable to be consie because",
          option_one: "chances of typographic errors are less",
          option_two: "it may be processed by assembler, loader etc which may have their own rules that may contradict the language rules",
          option_three: "Both option A and B",
          option_four: "None of the mentioned",
          answer: "C",
          explanation: ""
            },
      ],

      mcq6: [
        {
          id: "6",
          subject_name: "CP",
          chapter_name: "Mcqs in CS",
          question: "The minimum number of temporary variables needed to swap the contents of two variables is",
          option_one: "1",
          option_two: "2",
          option_three: "3",
          option_four: "0",
          answer: "D",
          explanation: ""
            },
      ],
      mcq7: [
        {
          id: "7",
          subject_name: "CP",
          chapter_name: "Mcqs in CS",
          question: "The purpose of the following program fragement <br> <img src='images/cp2.webp'> <br> where s,b are ingeters ",
          option_one: "transfer the content of s to b",
          option_two: "transfer the content of b to s",
          option_three: "exchange(swap) the contents of s and b",
          option_four: "negate the contents of s and b",
          answer: "C",
          explanation: ""
            },
      ],
      mcq8: [
        {
          id: "8",
          subject_name: "CP",
          chapter_name: "Mcqs in CS",
          question: "Let a,b be two non-negative integers. The call to find(a, find(a, b)) can be used to find. <img src='images/cp1.webp'>",
          option_one: "maximum of a, b",
          option_two: "positive difference of a, b",
          option_three: "sum of a, b",
          option_four: "minimum of a, b",
          answer: "D",
          explanation: ""
            },
      ],
      mcq9: [
        {
          id: "9",
          subject_name: "CP",
          chapter_name: "Mcqs in CS",
          question: "Let a,b be two non-negative integers. which of the following calls, finds the positive differernce of a and b",
          option_one: "find(a,b) + find(b,a)",
          option_two: "find(a, find(a,b))",
          option_three: "c + find(a,b)",
          option_four: "b + find(a,b)",
          answer: "A",
          explanation: ""
            },
      ],
      mcq10: [
        {
          id: "10",
          subject_name: "CP",
          chapter_name: "Mcqs in CS",
          question: "If integer needs two bytes of storage, then maximum value of an unsigned integer is",
          option_one: "2<sup> 16</sup> - 1",
          option_two: "2<sup> 15</sup> - 1",
          option_three: "2<sup> 16</sup>",
          option_four: "2<sup> 15</sup>",
          answer: "A",
          explanation: ""
            },
      ],


}
